http://www.sentinelgroup.com.au/privacy-policy.php

Contact us
Be involved without the workload.
View our Client App
Central to the success of Sentinel Financial Group is our commitment to our clients. We honour without reservation our obligation to respect and protect the privacy of the personal information of individuals with whom we deal.
The information we collect
Whenever it is reasonable and practicable to do so, we only collect information about you directly from you.
We only collect personal information about you which is reasonably necessary to:
provide you quality products or services
consider applications and approaches you make to us
maintain your contact details
We generally hold personal information relating to:
the products and services we provide or have provided to you
your financial interests and sometimes your financial position
your contact details
We do not generally collect sensitive information about you unless required by applicable laws or rules. Sensitive information includes information relating to:
race
political or religious beliefs
sexual preferences
criminal convictions
membership of professional or trade associations or unions
health information
How that information is used
We only use and disclose personal information about you for the purpose for which it was disclosed to us or related purposes which would reasonably be expected without your permission.
For example, we may from time to time use your personal information to inform you of investment opportunities or to provide information about products and services which we expect may be of interest to you. However, we do respect your right to ask us not to do this.
We do not sell personal information to other organisations to allow them to do this.
We may disclose personal information to service providers who provide services in connection with our products and services or we may provide information about you to your nominated financial adviser with your permission.
Keeping information accurate and up to date
We take all reasonable steps to ensure that all information we hold is as accurate as is possible. You are able to contact us at any time and ask for its correction if you feel the information we have about you is inaccurate or incomplete.
Keeping information secure
We use security procedures and the latest technology to protect the information we hold. Access to and use of personal information within Sentinel Financial Group is appropriately limited to prevent misuse or unlawful disclosure of the information.
If other organisations provide support services, we require them to appropriately safeguard the privacy of the information provided to them.
Where the personal information we collect is no longer required, we delete the information or permanently de-identify it.
How you can access your information
You can contact us to request access to your information. In normal circumstances we will give you full access to your information. However, there may be some legal or administrative reasons to deny access. If access is denied, we will provide you with the reason why.
Cookies
A 'cookie' is a packet of information placed on a user's computer by a website for record keeping purposes. Cookies are generally used on the Sentinel Financial Group site to:
access online services - if you visit Sentinel Financial Group's website and log into our secure areas, such as Sentinel Financial Group Portal, we will use cookies to enable us to authorise your access
traffic monitoring - we use tracking companies to gather information about how people are using the Sentinel Financial Group site, this information includes time of visit, pages visited, and some system information about the type of computer you are using. We use this information to enhance the content and services offered on the site.
Cookies may also be used for other purposes on the Sentinel Financial Group site but in each case none of the information collected can be used to personally identify you.
You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is sent.
(Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences).
If you disable the use of cookies on your web browser or remove or reject specific cookies from this website or linked sites then you may not be able to gain access to all of the content and facilities in this website.
Dealing with Sentinel Financial Group online
If you visit Sentinel Financial Group's website to browse, read or download information, our system will log these movements. These web site logs are not personally identifiable and Sentinel Financial Group makes no attempt to link them with the individuals who browse the site.
Sentinel Financial Group cannot guarantee or accept responsibility for the privacy practices or the content of web sites to which we provide links.
Contact us
If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy or handling of information, please contact us!
Take control of your financial future! Speak to Sentinel
+61 8 9225 0000
Sentinel Financial Group Pty Ltd (ABN 26 104 456 288) is authorised to provide financial services under its Australian Financial Services License (No. 230542). Privacy Policy. Disclaimer. FSG.
©Copyright 2005 - 2020 Sentinel Financial Group Pty Ltd. All rights reserved.
